Hi, I'm
Sarnathya. I'm from
Palaji. I completed my schooling at ARB International
School and I'm currently pursuing my Bachelor of
Technology at
Sreyeswar. I have strong technical skills in C,
C++ and
Java. I love to do coding and develop
small
applications. I'm a quick learner and always interested
in improving
myself. I do coding on regular basis to
improve my fundamentals and love to take up
small challenges which help me think
better. I'm open to learning new things and
technologies which help me better myself and improve
myself. My goal is to become a software
developer and contribute to innovation and
technologies. Thank
you.